learning-theories.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Learning Theories

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Learning-Theories.com collects, and the ways in which we use that personal information.

**Collection of Personal Information**

Learning-Theories.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: information about your use of this website, including usage statistics, geographic location, demographic details; information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including your name, email address, and other supplied information); information about transactions carried out over this website (including your credit card and other financial details); information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services;

**Using Personal Information**

Learning-Theories.com may use your personal information to administer this website; personalize the website for you and create a more customized experience; enable your access to and use of the website services; send to you products that you purchase; supply to you services that you purchase; send to you statements and invoices; collect payments from you; and send you marketing communications.

Where Learning-Theories.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Learning-Theories.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing Your Data**

We assert that Learning-Theories.com will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  We will store all the personal information you provide on secure servers; information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

**Updates**

At any time, Learning-Theories.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other Websites**

This website contains links to other websites that are not affiliated with Learning-Theories.com.  Learning-Theories.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

Also check out:
